[{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678836927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":14779,"timeElapsed":46830},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678843776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":6847,"timeElapsed":53679},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678846317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2539,"timeElapsed":56219},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678849506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3188,"timeElapsed":59409},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678855422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5915,"timeElapsed":65325},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678859859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4436,"timeElapsed":69762},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678862737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":72640},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678868115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5377,"timeElapsed":78018},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678871828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3712,"timeElapsed":81731},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678878835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5814,"timeElapsed":88737},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678881983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3147,"timeElapsed":91886},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678884553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2569,"timeElapsed":94456},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678886446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1892,"timeElapsed":96349},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678889047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2600,"timeElapsed":98950},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678890936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1888,"timeElapsed":100839},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678892722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1784,"timeElapsed":102625},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678894967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2245,"timeElapsed":104870},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678897592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2624,"timeElapsed":107495},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678906048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7511,"timeElapsed":115951},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678907694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1645,"timeElapsed":117597},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678909834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2139,"timeElapsed":119737},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678911494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1659,"timeElapsed":121397},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678913472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1978,"timeElapsed":123375},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678915516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2043,"timeElapsed":125419},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678917462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1944,"timeElapsed":127365},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678920044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2581,"timeElapsed":129947},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678923598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3553,"timeElapsed":133501},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678930085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5420,"timeElapsed":139988},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678931748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1662,"timeElapsed":141651},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678933978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2229,"timeElapsed":143881},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678935714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":145617},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678937661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1946,"timeElapsed":147564},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678939495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1833,"timeElapsed":149398},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678941352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1856,"timeElapsed":151255},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678945242,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3889,"timeElapsed":155145},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12516,"timeElapsed":167661},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678959532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1772,"timeElapsed":169435},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5695,"timeElapsed":175965},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678967752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1689,"timeElapsed":177655},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678969443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1690,"timeElapsed":179346},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678971063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1619,"timeElapsed":180965},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1878,"timeElapsed":182844},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678975584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":185487},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678977839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2254,"timeElapsed":187742},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678981250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3410,"timeElapsed":191153},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678986339,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5088,"timeElapsed":196242},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678993650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7309,"timeElapsed":203553},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9427,"timeElapsed":213947},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2134,"timeElapsed":216082},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3575,"timeElapsed":219658},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679011443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1686,"timeElapsed":221346},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679013297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1853,"timeElapsed":223200},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679014895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1598,"timeElapsed":224798},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679017360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2463,"timeElapsed":227263},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679019423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2062,"timeElapsed":229326},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679020966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1542,"timeElapsed":230869},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679023957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2180,"timeElapsed":233860},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679025953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1995,"timeElapsed":235856},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679030512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4559,"timeElapsed":240415},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":243782},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2177,"timeElapsed":245960},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":26570,"timeElapsed":272532},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679065569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2939,"timeElapsed":275472},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":19989,"timeElapsed":295462},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2136,"timeElapsed":297598},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6538,"timeElapsed":305034},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":72950,"timeElapsed":377986},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2264,"timeElapsed":380251},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":42899,"timeElapsed":423151},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679216177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2928,"timeElapsed":426080},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679218270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2092,"timeElapsed":428173},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4553,"timeElapsed":432727},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":27951,"timeElapsed":460679},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679252886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2109,"timeElapsed":462789},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679257458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3637,"timeElapsed":467361},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679259404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1946,"timeElapsed":469307},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2565,"timeElapsed":471874},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679264182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2210,"timeElapsed":474085},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1614,"timeElapsed":475700},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679268236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2438,"timeElapsed":478139},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679269920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1683,"timeElapsed":479823},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679271697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1776,"timeElapsed":481600},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679273716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2018,"timeElapsed":483619},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":24209,"timeElapsed":508791},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679300811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1922,"timeElapsed":510714},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679302879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2067,"timeElapsed":512782},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2668,"timeElapsed":515451},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679307878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":517781},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679309737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1858,"timeElapsed":519640},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679315506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5768,"timeElapsed":525409},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679317838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2331,"timeElapsed":527741},{"subjectID":"fv01c8facz","prolificID":"675597aa8edbd645627043a1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3d07f0abb2253c587c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679321017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3177,"timeElapsed":530920}]